Do you think?
- Do you want to test mine?
- Yes.
- My spray tastes raspberries.
- It's blue?
Yes, I know, but it's a raspberry here on the package, so ... Yes, it's raspberries.
This one should be strawberry.
It does not taste strawberry.
It tastes sour.
This one should be green apple.
You might imagine that it tastes a little green apple.
Do you also want to test now, Laura?
What grades do you give from 1 to 5?
null
- Or wait, 0 to 5. - Yes.
- 5. - 5?!
Laura, how many points do you give?
"Um."
One.
One, one, one, one, one.
“Cotton Candy Buttered Popcorn Flaves”
So it is sugar candy with a taste of buttery popcorn.
- So nasty texture.
- Uh!
Is it common to be able to buy sugar candy in a chip bag?
- I do not know.
"Made in the USA," this says.
- Exciting.
Okay.
- Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
Oh!
It really tastes popcorn with butter flavor.
No.
What sick!
- Laura does not seem to like.
- No.
She takes back her candy deodorant.
- I think this was good.
- You like this?
It was something completely new to me.
Not my thing.
So ... I'm shocked.
I don't know what I was thinking, but not this.
- OH!
There is something sour and runny inside!
- No, then.
Stop it.
Hello, you haven't even eaten by yours!
- This is the worst Halloween candy.
- Yes!
You mean, "Worst disgusting Halloween candy"?
Yes, it was a bit disgusting to eat.
- So, why is it red?
- It's the blood.
"Creepy."
(scary)
I give this 2 points because I love Halloween.
I give the same, 2 points, because it is a good Halloween candy to give to children who want to run bus or sweets.
- eww.
0 points.
- "eww."
He throws eyes here.
"Mentos Fanta"
It is quite common mento -caramel that are orange.
- Wow!
- It really tastes Fanta.
- Yes, it really does.
But now you have to put away your eyes.
What does what you have taste like in your mouth?
Fanta without carbonic acid.
Was it good?
Waaah ...
I think this tastes just like regular orange mentosis.
No, it doesn't.
That's why I give this 0 points.
It was just a "rebranding" of an old product.
No.
- Horrible!
- Ah, I'm crying.
Horrible!
- Eww!
- Oh, my eye.
Eww!
- You get sweaty on the eyelids of this candy.
- You get sweaty everywhere.
I give this chewing gum 3.5 point in terms of taste.
And I actually think this candy deserves "Crazy points."
I give it 4 "Crazy points."
Yes, it was very "crazy."
It only gets "crazy points" from me, 2 pieces.
But 0 for taste.
I give the type 4 "Crazy points," For it was pretty "Crazy."
It looked like shrek-bay.
And then it was like ... The taste of it was not so good, so I give it a third.